<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Baggerspion</title>
    <description>Paul Adams' Wanderings Around Engineering, Free Software and Berlin</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000//</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 21:39:40 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 21:39:40 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.3.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Baggerspion</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I have set myself a challenge for 2017: write at least one blog post
every week. Given that I only managed to write 11 in 2016, this should
pose quite a challenge. Before &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; challenge there was something
else to tackle: &lt;a href=&quot;http://baggerspion.net&quot;&gt;baggerspion.net&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;historical-note&quot;&gt;Historical Note&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have been bloggng for a while. I started when I was studying for my
PhD, well over a decade ago now. Back then my department hosted my
blog on crappy (even for the time), old Linux server called
Hemswell. The blog was called “Green Eggs and Ham” back then. Don’t
ask.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Honestly, then my memory gets fuzzy; there is a gap of a year or two
before the first incarnation of Baggerspion. Baggerspion started life
as a Wordpress blog. It was self-hosted on a Linux VM that also
provided a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.kolab.org&quot;&gt;Kolab Groupware&lt;/a&gt; server.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the start of 2016 I decided to get rid of that VM and everything it
did. Baggerspion email was migrated to Google and the blog to
&lt;a href=&quot;http://blogger.com&quot;&gt;Blogger&lt;/a&gt; with it. Blogger, quite simply, it
terrible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;something-new&quot;&gt;Something New&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I decided that it was time for yet another (hopefully long-term)
change: to move Baggerpsion to
&lt;a href=&quot;http://pages.github.com&quot;&gt;GithubPages&lt;/a&gt;. This gives me an opportunity
to learn some new tools (in the form of &lt;a href=&quot;http://travis-ci.org&quot;&gt;Travis
CI&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;). I am
actually writing this post before the new site is even ready. Having a
“real” entry like this helps me to learn my new tools and to make sure
the site looks right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;whats-involved&quot;&gt;What’s Involved?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Github Pages: for hosting&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Jekyll: for generating the site&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Travis CI: for quality control of builds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;meet-the-new-baggerspion-same-as-the-old-baggerspion&quot;&gt;Meet The New Baggerspion, Same As The Old Baggerspion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contentwise, it’s business as usual. Baggerspion will continue to be
my home for writing about software engineering (management),
publishing weird visualisations of what’s goign on inside Free
Software projects and generally striving to be interesting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am treating this as a completely new start. You can still find the
old Baggerspion content &lt;a href=&quot;http://baggerspion.blogspot.com&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. Once
I have this post published, my first real content will be on the Crate
1.0.x release.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 21:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//2016/12/new-baggerspion/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//2016/12/new-baggerspion/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Baggerspion</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
